Reprintsev Roman

backend developer

Moscow, RU 123007 +7 (999) 6-729-729 doberbeatz@gmail.com

doberbeatz.github.io linkedin.com/in/doberbeatz

Personal Summary

Backend Developer with 3-year background in the website industry.



SKILLS

PHP (5.3-7) · Laravel (4.3-5.1) · Zend 1 · Symfony 2+ · Bitrix CMS

Blade · Twig

JavaScript · CSS · HTML · jQuery · Bootstrap · Less · Sass · Gulp

MySQL · PostgreSQL · Memcached · Redis

Unix · Docker · Fabric · Consul

Python (Django, Flask) · Java

OOP · Design Patterns

REST · JSON-RPC

Nginx · Apache · GIT

Agile · Scrum · Jira · PHPStorm · PyCharm · Vim

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Languages Interests

English Music Russian Movies

Uzbek Books (Technical)

Video Games

Professional goals

Development Trav

Sport Travel

Tasty Food

WORK EXPERIENCE

August 2016 - present

Banki.ru PHP DEVELOPER

Moscow, Russia

PHP 5.6-7, Symfony 2-3, Yii 1, Bitrix CMS, PostgreSQL, Git, Memcached, Redis, Rabbit MQ, Jira, Bitbucket

Responsibilities:

- Building new features
- Moving old code from Bitrix CMS into Symfony Framework
- Refactoring old code
- Optimizing DB queries
- Add new services into SOA system
- Fix bugs
- Code review

Accomplishments:

- Several big modules has been moved from Bitrix CMS into Symphony
- Old code that worked with DB extracted into services (Symfony, Yii)
- Website's speed has been increased due the upgrade PHP version to 7 and optimize DB queries
- Got experience working with 500k vps project
- Learned to DB indexing and shared this with my colleagues as a lecture
- Learned to Symfony Components
- Learned and got practice with old code refactoring

October 2014 - August 2016

Imagespark PHP DEVELOPER

Moscow, Russia

PHP 5.3-7, Laravel 4-5, Zend 1, MySQL, Redis, Vagrant, Bitrix CMS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Responsibilities:

- Building web projects from scratch based on Laravel Framework
- Maintaining existing web projects based on Laravel and Zend Framework
- Building and maintaining new modules/packages for each project
- Building REST API for mobile apps
- Working within "Vagrant" environment, using "Homestead" machine by Laravel
- Designing DB structure and writing migrations
- Projects deploying
- Projects managing
- Sometimes working remotely using VPN and SSH
- Helping to Juniors

Accomplishments:

- Got good practice with OOP and Design Patterns
- Learned to Laravel and Zend frameworks
- Completed big part of lessons on Laracasts paid by the company
- Built plenty web projects based on Laravel Framework
- Successfully completed the project for the mobile version Tattooz (m.tattooz.ru)
- Successfully completed the project CRMM (crmm.ru)
- Successfully completed the sub-project for Sberbank (sberbank-school.ru)
- Successfully integrated the redesign for Volkswagen (my.vw.ru)

WORK EXPERIENCE

February 2014 - October 2014

QSOFT
PHP DEVELOPER

PHP 5.3-7, Laravel 4-5, Zend 1, MySQL, Redis, Vagrant, Bitrix CMS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Responsibilities:

- Integration HTML layout into Bitrix CMS
- Building custom components
- Maintaining existing code
- Maintaining JavaScript code (¡Query + AJAX)
- Committing changes using Git CVS

Accomplishments:

- Learned to PHP, Bitrix CMS, SQL, Vim, Git
- Learned to working with Linux console
- Got practice with Ubuntu and Debian
- Learned to team working
- Successfully completed several projects based on Bitrix CMS
- Graduated 2 stages of training employees

EDUCATION

October 2011 - June 2014

BACHELOR DEGREE

PPU, Institute of International Tourism Administration

SOCIOCULTURAL SERVICE AND TOURISM

Moscow, Russia

September 2006 - June 2009

ASSOCIATE DEGREE

Tashkent Professional College of Information Technology

INFORMATION COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY SYSTEMS WITH A BUSINESS FOCUS

Tashkent, Uzbekistan